

ÖMER F. DOĞAN

Web Developer & Designer

I am a web developer who loves the develop myself and give high performance to my projects. I'm good at MVC structure, angular, react.js, node.js, php and frameworks, responsive design, testing and debugging, UX-UI design and analytical skills from different sectors (Healthcare, Medical, Advertisement, Tourism, E-Commerce and Game). I am open to all kind of research and development projects.

SKILLS

COMPUTER SKILLS:

- Angular
- React
- Python
- C#
- PHP
- Node.js
- SQL
- Flutter
- Firebase
- Html
- CSS
- Javascript
- MVC
- React Native
- Adobe PS,AI,XD
- Excel

CONTACT

omerfarukdoganweb@gmail.com



+90 541 635 9202

Pendik / ISTANBUL

EDUCATION

Istanbul Gedik University, Istanbul, Turkey

(September 2019-Present)
Computer Programming

Yakacık Vocational High School, Istanbul, Turkey

(September 2015-June 2019)
 Information Technology

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER & DESIGNER (JUN 2020 - Present)

Pigleb E-Commerce & Software Solutions - Freelance

CHAIRMAN OF COMPUTER SOCIETY (DEC 2019 - Present)

IEEE Istanbul Gedik University Student Branch

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (JUN 2019 - Present)

Grapware Digital - Freelance

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (JUL 2018 - AUG 2018)

Aras Kargo - Intern

IT SUPPORT TECHNICIAN (JUL 2017 - AUG 2017)

Orjin Engineering - Intern

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Fundamentals of Digital Marketing Google
- Google Analytics for Beginners Google
- Python Solutions Hackerrank

VOLUNTARY

Kızılay

(February 2019-June 2020)

TEMA Foundation

(February 2019-June 2020)

AFAD

(September 2020- Present)

IEEE Member / Volunteer

(May 2019- Present)

REFERENCES

Dr. Şenay Kocakoyun Aydoğan

Istanbul Gedik University, Dr.

Mert Topuz

Kolay Gelsin, Human Resources Manager

Fuat Arslan

Bluetel, Technical Manager

Contact information of references available upon request.